export const triviaData = [
  {
    question: "Whose bedsheets are The Wheel of Time themed?",
    options: ["Beta Eclipse", "Decimition", "UnboltingEnd", "HaveAKnivesDay"],
    correctAnswer: "Beta Eclipse",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who refused to do the fantasy football punishment two years in a row?",
    options: ["Dectrix", "Baby Jesus ", "Decimition", "Beta Eclipse"],
    correctAnswer: "Baby Jesus",
  },
  {
    question: "Which two blokes yap about the Stormlight Archive?",
    options: [
      "HaveAKnivesDay and Jameson",
      "Beta Eclipse and Dectrix ",
      "Baby Jesus and Millie",
      "UnboltingEnd and Sean",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Beta Eclipse and Dectrix",
  },
  {
    question: "Who uses their freewill to NOT play pickleball with the boys?",
    options: ["Jameson", "UnboltingEnd", "Beta Eclipse", "HaveAKnivesDay"],
    correctAnswer: "Beta Eclipse",
  },
  {
    question: "Which amigo drives with no shoes (whack)? ",
    options: ["Jameson", "Decimition", "Dectrix", "HaveAKnivesDay"],
    correctAnswer: "Jameson",
  },
  {
    question: "Who could not ride a Dune Sandworm? ",
    options: ["UnboltingEnd", "HaveAKnivesDay", "Jameson", "Dectrix"],
    correctAnswer: "UnboltingEnd",
  },
  {
    question: "How did The Rat House get its name?",
    options: [
      "One of the amigos living there was a rat",
      "Underground rat fighting ring",
      "Blokes love cheese",
      "One of the 10 trials was defeating a family of rats",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "One of the 10 trials was defeating a family of rats",
  },
  {
    question: "Which shaved little yard gnome coined the term lil amigo?",
    options: ["HaveAKnivesDay", "Decimition", "Beta Eclipse", "Jameson"],
    correctAnswer: "Decimition",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Thomas S. aka JusticeAlwaysPrevails?",
    options: [
      "Lord of the Rings bloke",
      "13th Disciple",
      "UnboltingEnd's rareform",
      "The light that exposed the world",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The light that exposed the world",
  },
  {
    question: "Most memorable home of the blokes?",
    options: ["The Rat House", "Egg Townhouse", "Nole Quarters"],
    correctAnswer: "Nole Quarters",
  },
  {
    question: "Game of Thrones biggest fan?",
    options: [
      "HaveAKnivesDay",
      "HaveAKnivesDay",
      "HaveAKnivesDay",
      "HaveAKnivesDay",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "HaveAKnivesDay",
  },

  // Add more trivia questions and answers here
];

export default triviaData;
